{
  "decks": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "name": "Rendering in React",
      "description": "React's component structure allows for quickly building a complex web application that relies on DOM manipulation. "
    }
  ],
  "cards": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "front": "Differentiate between Real DOM and Virtual DOM.",
      "back": "Virtual DOM updates are faster but do not directly update the HTML",
      "deckId": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "sdgfgdg",
      "back": "asdgdfgdfgdsfg",
      "id": 2
    },
    {
      "front": "edit test",
      "back": "edit test",
      "id": 3
    },
    {
      "cards": [],
      "front": "b",
      "back": "b",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 7
    },
    {
      "front": "this is a test",
      "back": "this is the success",
      "id": 20
    },
    {
      "front": "isfhfsihfofughdghdog",
      "back": "dfkhsdoguhgu",
      "deckId": 1,
      "id": 21
    },
    {
      "front": "this is a new test",
      "back": "same old success",
      "id": 22
    },
    {
      "front": "this is the edited test card",
      "back": "this is the edited test card's success",
      "id": 23
    },
    {
      "front": "this is the edited test card",
      "back": "this is the back of the edited test card",
      "id": 24
    },
    {
      "front": "this is the edited test card",
      "back": "this is the back of the edited test card",
      "id": 25
    }
  ]
}